Folks, today's session
is going to be
Today's session is going to be on AI agents and routing, right? Agents is a buzzword. It's the most important topic probably throughout the
Entire cohort, okay.
To give you a recap.
We discussed chunking strategies, dock, LangChain
Hybrid RAG
SQL, RAG, etc last weekend
All of you, I hope all of you remember what we learned during the last session. Does anyone remember what is the primary purpose of dockling
Just type in chat, what's the primary use of DocLink library
See, they can ask you this kind of question in the interview, okay, why do you use lock link? Sometimes, you know, you know, but you don't know how to explain or how to type in
Yeah, chunking docks and so parsing, mainly SERP
You have PDFs with weird structures, tables. You want to parse it and extract data that is
That is the main purpose, okay, and what is the purpose of LangChain
Yes, it's a framework to build AI applications, okay? So now let's dive into the main topic, which is
What exactly is an AI agent
You all have heard this term, right? So you tell me, like, can you give me one short, precise definition of AI agent
See, everyone knows about AI agent, but I want you to give me one short, very precise definition
Okay, LLM with access to tools
So, Sai Sriram, LLM with access to tools
Is correct, but there is one piece missing in that
Which Abhiram mentioned, which is action, right, do task.
Software 00 is a James Bond of software world, right?
With anatomy, okay, most of you know it already, so let's, just in case if you're not aware, let's dive into this
When you type this kind of query in ChatGPT
Show me flight prices from New York to Chicago for tomorrow. Will it be able to answer it?
Will it be able to answer the question here
Yeah, yes, it can answer. But do you notice something weird here? It is saying surging eating website, you know.
It says searching websites, searching internet, and so on.
Internally.
It will use some model, let's say GPT 5.3
Or GPT
5.4 okay it will use some kind of model. This one is GPT 5.3.
And if you Google
GPT 5.3 knowledge cutoff
Then it says August 31, 2025.
Today, it's August 30
So, ChatGPT is powered by a model like this. And if I ask
If I have a plane model, if I have a plane GPD 5.3 model
And if I ask it for a flight price for tomorrow, this is not me one, let's say from New York to Chicago tomorrow, right, if I ask for that flight price
It won't be able to answer it because
Its knowledge is frozen in time
I hope you all are aware that when the Frontier Labs train these models
They train it on a huge amount of data
And there is a training cutoff
So at some point, so let's say the model training finishes on some point
That would have a knowledge until only certain point of time
So the question is
Why does it answer the question? If LLM's model knowledge is
Frozen in time
How does it answer the question? Okay, tools, exactly. So we already saw
In this that
When you are doing this, see, it is searching 18 websites
So it is calling some tools, okay?
So, it is calling, let's say, internet
And using the internet, it can pull the information.
So what we just saw is an example of
LLM
Calling tools, and tools can be anything. It can be API call, it can be
It can be like variety of tools. So here it is calling internet and it is pulling the
information for you
Now
Can we call ChatGPT an agent?
See, ChatGPT… okay, so ChatGPT, if you connect it with, like, Google and so on
It can perform agentic applications, but the use case that we just saw
Where we are asking a question, it is using tools and using tools. It is retrieving me flight
App prices. Can I call this system agent
Okay, a couple of people are saying no, okay, Gauru, Anupam, you're saying no, Poojan, you are saying no. Why?
Why can't you call it agent? Because it is calling tools
So it is Llan plus 2. Why can't you call it an agent?
Exactly, folks. See, Ash is exactly right
Ashis Sarath, it can't take action, it is still Q&A, correct?
But let's take another example. You have Amazon's Refus chatbot. I want to buy organic honey with 4.5 rating
Less than $20 price
And when I type in that question
It will show me the products, then I can say add it to the cart
I can also say
Check out, and it places the order for you, okay? Now, can I call this chatbot an agent?
Yeah, I can call it. Why? Because it can place order for me. See, check out now, you see
So, essentially what's happening here is
When you give this kind of question
There is LLM. So LLM is like a brain of the system.
It knows that it has to find products
With 4.5 plus rating and less than $20 price, so it will have access to some kind of products database. It will have access to some kind of reviews API
Using this, it will pull all the products using Reviews API, it will filter the products with 4.5 plus rating, and it will show you list of
Products
Then
When you say
Buy the first one for me. See, now, when I say buy the first one for me
It has a memory of my old question
See, if you look at this question in isolation, then LLM will get confused, okay? See, LLM folks, remember LLM itself doesn't have memory.
LLM is trained on vast amount of data. So it has
That knowledge inbuilt in its brain, but it doesn't have additional memory to remember your past questions and so on. Memory is something you have to
Provide it as an external thing, okay.
So since now this green box, so look at this green box, so this green box is a system where we have LLM
You have reviews API, you have products
And you also have memory
Through this memory, it remembers that I asked this question and I know that I have to
Place an order for the first product, which is this Whole Foods 365 honey. Okay, and then it will have access to another API, which is the checkout API
Using which it will place an order for you
So the green box here is an agent here, okay?
So, this is a specific example for
Amazon's roughest chatbot. If you want to make it generic, you can make it like this
You have LLM
You have tools
Knowledge
And memory, okay? So agent is equal to LLM
Plus twos plus knowledge plus memory but one piece is missing here, right? I should probably have 1 more plus, which is what
You all know it, which is
Autonomous action
We'll go deeper into autonomy
In a bit
But
This is what an agent is. It's a program that takes input
Things and acts
To complete a task in autonomous way
Using tools, memory, and knowledge
Take a moment
Look at the equation
Look at the definition, okay, try to grasp it. This is the most fundamental concept in the
I would say this is the core, most important, most fundamental concept in the entire cohort
Because the whole world is going crazy about agents
So, Sarath is asking how is action different from tool calling?
So see, tool calling is done by LLM
An LLM needs some information. Let's say it needs APIs. It needs knowledge.
It needs to access memory, so these are the tool calls
But action is the
Is the overarching goal
So my goal, see, action is performed by agent.
Tool calling is done by your LLM, right? So action is performed by agent. It is higher level goal that user has given to your agent.
To accomplish the goal
Your agent is making tool calls. It's like if you call Carpenter to build a chair in your home
Then you are calling Carpenter that build a chair, okay? So that is
Basically, an action, so let's say
Here it is you
Okay
And here is Mr. Carpenter.
So here is my carpenter.
So, you are calling Carpenter
Build chair
So, this is an action
This is an action.
Carpenter is going to build the chair. Now, Carpenter will use hammer
Right? They will use screwdriver
Right?
They will use screwdrivers, they will use nail
They will
Cut the wood with some tool
So Carpenter
is using all these tools. So when Carpenter is using a hammer to put a nail in your chair, that is tool calling
When they're cutting the wood with this
Equipment with this tool that is tool calling
But you are building a chair, so the process of building chair is called action, okay
So, in the system that we saw
Agent will do step-by-step reasoning. When you say
See, if you go to Amazon's chatbot, you can directly give this command.
Buy me the best rated honey from Amazon. It should be organic. If you do that, it will search, it will put it in the cart, it will check out, it will place the order
So it is doing
Step by step reasoning, it is doing multi-step reasoning, okay, so it is first
finding out organic honey from the products database, then it is filtering the ones which has less than 4.5 rating. Then it is adding it to cart
Placing an order and so on, so it is doing multi-step reasoning
Multi-step planning, see this agent is still
A very
Basic agent, but you can have a complex travel agent also
Where you can say I want to fly to Italy in the month of May for 1 week, weather should be sunny. Find me a trip which cost me less than $5,000. I'm vegetarian. You can give that kind of complex prompt and it will do multi-step planning, multi-step reasoning to accomplish a higher level goal
And it works on this complex goal in an autonomous way. So we'll go into autonomy
Now, so see, what is autonomy? So, autonomy is essentially, I give you
This example of a carpenter
So you will as a user, you will supply some requirement to your carpenter. You will say
Build a chair
Okay, build a chair
You will give your dimension that it should be this by this
It should be wooden
Okay?
And I want to build it in less than 10,000 rupees.
Yeah, you give all the constraints and your requirements.
Then Carpenter will build the chair
Now, when carpenter is cutting the wood.
He's not going to ask you, how should I cut the wood, correct?
You don't provide instruction to carpenter that
This is how you should cut the wood. This is how you should paint the
Chair, this is how you should put the nail in the leg of a chair
Carpenter is autonomous. He knows, see
So he knows what he's doing. You don't spoon-fed him, so that is autonomy
So, same way when we have agent
We tell agent, I need organic honey, 4.5 rating less than
$20 price
After that, agent knows all this, you know how to find from ProductsDB how to add it, how to place to check out, how to place an order. Agent knows this.
So that is autonomy
Okay
Yes, Sandeep, carpenter can cross-check requirements. So when you're calling agent, let's say you know what is the most complex agent? Some agent that you use
Probably every day
Or maybe a few times a week
You know what is the most complex agent that you use in your life
Claude code, exactly folks
So, send it to your question, Carpenter can cross-check requirement, right? When you write code with Claude code, does it ask you question
Does it ask you questions that do this? It does, right? It will say, okay, I'm going to assume this
Can I access your files? You know, you get all the prompts. You say yes, no, yes, no. Sometimes it gives you option. These are the four options, okay, for this, I will use FastAPI or Flask. Which one do you prefer? You say yes, this one.
So that is same as Carpenter asking the questions.
So there are two important characteristics of an AI agent. It uses LLM as a brain, and it has autonomy.
So
Autonomy
Here means let me take a different example
They say, so I am from a village, so I'm going to use some farming example.
So we have this farm
So this is, let's say, my farm in my village.
Okay?
So we have this nice crop
Okay.
All of that. And on the side
We have a cow, so let me draw the cow here.
So these are the four legs, okay
I used to get
First rank in drawing, so you can see how beautiful my cow is. This is the tail.
And you tie the cow with some kind of pole, so there is a pole, and you have tied your cow with a rope
Now, you have put a bucket of water for the cow
You have put some food here
Okay?
And cow can graze
She can go around in this particular periphery, okay? So this is the boundary for the cow, because it's a rope, right? So it's a… it's a circle.
So cow is autonomous
Crow is autonomous
Autonomous
In a sense that
If cow feels hungry, she will go eat the food, she will drink the water, she will sit, relax
You're not going to instruct Ka, okay? Hey cow, sleep, hey cow, do this. Cow is autonomous in that sense
But it also has boundaries, folks
So let's say there is a road here
Okay
And some vehicles are passing by.
Can cow go to that road? No, right? Because you have a rope, you have tied the cow to the to the pole
Can cow go and spoil your crop you know you're about to harvest your crop. Can she do that
No, because you have a rope
So this rope is nothing but guardrail and a boundary, right, guardrail
This is for safety. You need to have guardrails, you need to have boundaries.
So that it doesn't take autonomous action outside the boundaries that you have defined, okay
It doesn't go on a road and hit the vehicle, you know, it doesn't go to a nearby farm
Your neighbor's farm with you… with whom you had quarrels
On silly topic
It doesn't go and spoil the crop in your neighbor's farm. So that is the guardrail, but still cow is autonomous in a sense that
It can still eat, it can drink water, and so on, so rope is a guardrail gotham, exactly. So we have to understand that when you are defining an agent
Establishing guardrails is super important.
We will have a separate entire session on guardrails because this is an extremely important topic.
Right? So there were recent incidents in the industry where agents broke out of their guardrails and they did crazy things. Does anyone know that incident?
Does anyone know the incident where cow broke the rope and went to neighbors farm and did some damage?
OpenAI and Hugging Face. Yes, Anurag, exactly.
So OpenAI
Was training this model for which was good in a cybersecurity
And that model broke out of their guardrails. It went to Hugging Face website.
And it hacked it
See, how bad is that, right? So even if you define guardrails
Agents can break out of that system. So as an AI engineer, it is your
It is your duty. Your duty of utmost importance to make sure your guardrails are solid and strong
You don't want to give your agent a chance
To break out of those guardrails. Otherwise, it can delete a rack code in a production database
It can perform a transaction you don't want it to perform.
It can post something stupid
On the social feed, or in the chat board, talking to your customer, that can completely
Spoil the brand reputation of your company
Alright?
So autonomy can be
You can give
Agent and autonomy to read and write files
You can allow it to make a bank transaction. It can
Send emails, it can delete and create things, but it has to be protected
You all are smart
And you would
Immediately infer that as you increase the autonomy or agency
Of an agent, the predictability will go down
Correct?
So this is agency. Agency or autonomy
Okay
The extent to which it can perform free action that is your agency.
So as you increase the agency or autonomy of an agent, the predictability of it will go down
So if you want to plot different applications in this chart, then
The traditional ChatGPT, which is just a Q&A chat board, will come here now see chat GPT also is becoming agent nowadays, because if you connect it with ChatGPT and Claude, I have not tried ChatGPT, but I have tried Claude
Where you connect it with your Gmail, with your Slack, and if you say, okay, send an email to this person and so on, it will do that
Okay, so
Agency is kind of low in ChatGPT and therefore predictability is higher
But then you can build an agent using things like N8n, Zapier, etc.
Which can perform
The autonomous action for you
Then comes Claude Code if you give bypass permission, and if you give full autonomy, it will not even ask you question, it will just keep on building
And then there is one more thing, one more application. Can you suggest any application which is even more
Autonomous, then Claude code
Open claw, exactly. Open claw… see, open claw, there was a hype of open claw sometime back, now nobody is talking about open claw.
Now it's Hermes. Hermes is also now people are not talking, right? So see, this is how fast AI market is
Evolving, it's like things come, things just
Things just get out of attention on social media so fast.
Okay, but folks, remember
This particular thing. So it's a rag chat board routed workflow tool augmented chatbot AI agent. Okay?
Now, if you think about AI applications
There is 1 type of application which is Agentic AI application. Do you know other kind?
See, what we just saw, open claw
Claude code
Amazon's roughers
These are all agentic applications. But there is a second type. Do you all know? What is that second type?
Basically, non-agentic applications. So if you are, yes, exactly. It is called workflow
Just workflow, not agentic workflow, because if you have agentic workflow, then it's an agent.
So this is
Popular
Indian news channel
And nowadays news channels
Have this kind of quick summary
You all know, right? Have you… have you noticed this feature in news channels
Where they have
Quick summary, so that if you don't want to read the big news, you can get QuickBullet
Assume you are working in
NDTV
As an AI engineer and you want to build this system
How would you build it
See, previously, there was just news.
But now.
You have
The quick read of it, okay, so the way you build it is you have the actual news article, which is the article text
You do some pre-processing
And then you give it to LLM
Summarize it. So here, I'm saying, hey LLM, give me 3 bullet summary for this article
And once it gives summary, you will do some checks and generate summary and you will show it in the article.
Now see, here we are using LLM. Here LLM might be maybe calling a tool
Can we call this agentic
Is this an Agentic application?
No, right?
Because
There is no autonomous action
You are given… giving LLM a very well-defined task. You are giving LLM
An article. Okay, so my prompt
My prompt will look like
Generate
3 point summary, see 3 point
Summary
This
Article
And below here you just type in your article
And it will just generate a summary. So here LLM is performing a very well-defined task
It is not doing multi-step reasoning, multi-step planning. It is not calling tools and taking actions. Well, see.
Even if LLM calls tools, you can't… you can't call it Agentic unless it is doing
Action, autonomous action so autonomous action
Meaning, like, you know, performing some task or doing multi-step reasoning. It is not doing all of that.
So for that case, it will be it will not be agentic
And the pre-processing and post-processing is nothing but cleaning. So if you have worked in any NLP problem, right natural language processing problem, the article text that comes in the back end might have HTML tags, you know, it might have some redundant data. It might have information on, let's say, the author, the date
Etc
When you give it to LLM, you don't want to give article as is. So there'll be some text cleaning required. And when LLM generates the
Article like summary, maybe you want to do some post-processing, okay, so preprocessing, post-processing is usually common even when you're doing guardrails, you know there is input guardrail, output guardrail where you
Mask sensitive information, you make sure the output is not toxic and so on
We will go into these topics in the future session in detail, but for now, let's focus on this. It is
This second type of application is called a workflow. Now see workflow is a term that Anthropic came up with. You can use a different term as well. I mean, I like to call it non-agentic application.
And see, there is no, like, industry standard term here.
But you have to remember that 2 kind of applications Agentic application, non-agentic application, and non-agentic application is popularly known as workflow. Okay
Here once again, this can call tools, but
If LLM calls tools, that doesn't necessarily make it agentic. You can call it tool calling LLM, you know, tool calling system
Sometimes if you have chat board, which is calling tools, you can call it
tool augmented
Chatbot
Right? Chatbot is calling tools, but it's not performing action for you.
So you can't call it agent, but if chatbot is calling tools and if it is booking flight for you, for example, then it's an agent
Okay, the popular agent, as we all know, is Claude Code
Agent have this intrinsic behavior or intrinsic characteristic called react. React is reason
And act
When a user question comes, it will do some thinking
The LLM will do thinking. If you say, book a flight
It will do some thinking, reasoning, then it will take action, then it will do observation of its output
You all know you are using Claude Core, right? It will write the code. Then it makes mistakes. Has anyone noticed this? See, Claude code makes mistakes, but in the prompt you will see, oh, this thing is wrong. Let me go ahead and fix it.
Yeah, commonwealth Ashes, it does that. If you ask it to write code next time, observe it
You know, it keeps on typing, it will say writing code, running the code
Checking output, then you will say, oh, output doesn't conform to the requirement. Let me rewrite this file. So that is observation, and based on observation, it is again thinking, taking action.
Until the final goal is achieved, so this is essentially react loop for agents, okay
Now, there is this guide
From Anthropic
on building effective agents. So
You can check this article later on.
But I would like to show you this
So here
See, this is Anthropic's definition, right? Two types agents, workflows.
So workflows are system where LLM stores are orchestrated through predefined code paths. LLMs have a specific task, okay? It doesn't have much autonomy
And agents is this, okay, now
Let me show you
So, in the workflows, there are different types of workflows. There is prompt chaining.
Which means you call LLM and there is a gate and there is this kind of, you know, pass and fail
And then there is routing
So, in the routing, let's say if you have customer support chatbot
And if a question is
Related to technical support, it might call to another agent, which is doing technical support.
If the question is related to payments and a refund, it might route it to a different type of sub-agent
Or different type of LLM, let's say. Let us not go into multi-agent system yet.
And then if you have a question related to service or sales, right? So customer support chat board can have different kind of
They can receive a query with different category of intent. One intent might be technical support, one intent might be sales inquiry, one intent might be website support, payment, question, and so on
So whenever the first LLM is routing the calls to different LLMs, that workflow is called routing. So folks, you can have parallel also see you can have based on your question, you might want to call
Parallel LLMs and there might be aggregator. So check this
Check this when you get a chance
Okay, so we are now going to move into hands-on implementation. Once you have done hands-on implementation, we will open it up for questions. Okay, so let's write code. You will build understanding, and then we'll have a few minutes for the
Questions
All right, folks, so I'll quickly share the file with you.
Let me just share it in the chat.
And I know I saw a couple of messages asking for
executing code in VS Code, but…
That won't be feasible for everybody.
We are still going to use Colab for a few more days.
Okay? We will shift to VS4 when we feel like we are
We have enough knowledge of…
LLM applications and agents and all those things.
Before actually moving on to VSport.
So, here is the notebook I've shared.
Just…
Upload it on Google Full App, and…
Give me a thumbs up once you are all ready.
Okay? Alright.
So, we are going to install Langchain.
Langchain Grok, and we are going to install Landgraph.
I know we have not covered Langraph yet, but it is for… it is for a very small purpose, and you will see.
Why we need it? In a while.
Okay, so we will always start with…
our GRAW KPI keys. Let's add our Grog KPI keys, and…
instantiate a Chad Grog model.
Okay? So…
We have the Grok API key here, and we have just created a chat Grok model.
It is a simple model that is using GPT-OSS.
And we are telling the reasoning format first, because
It may have thinking tokens, so…
adding this, uh, reasoning format parsed,
is…
Folks were using Grok because it is free.
If you want to pay money, let us know, we'll use OpenAI. It's free and it is super, super convenient.
Yeah. Uh…
Cotton, we do not need a GPU for what we are going to do today.
Uh, if you are using Gronk API,
then your inference is happening on Grok servers, so you do not need a GPU for that.
Max retries is 2, because
If LLM is not able to generate response in the first,
try. It will try. I'm asking you just to try again.
Once more. Temperature is zero, everything is…
mentioned here. Uh, let's first see how we can do function calling, or tool calling with our LLMs.
Okay, so what is function calling?
you know that whenever we call any function,
We can represent the argument of that function.
in form of a dictionary, or in form of a JSON.
Right? We can have some parameter name as a keyword.
And whatever value.
we need to assign to that particular parameter, we can add it as a value here.
So, let's say you all just saw.
Dharvai showed you the screen of Yahoo Finance.
Where you saw NVIDIA ticker and everything, right?
We are going to build a finance agent today. That's why I said that we are not going off-topic.
it's actually very, uh, like, we are actually on topic, and uh…
what we need there is just covered.
some business knowledge that you need.
So you can see that, uh, I'm using this getStockFundamentals.
function, and…
Here, it has created an argument called ticker in NVIDIA, okay?
So, the whole goal of function calling is
to create these kind of JSON.
Because LLM can generate JSON, right?
These kind of JSON tell the name of the function that is to be used, and the arguments that are to be passed into that particular function.
Okay? If you are able to do this, then…
your, uh… you can say that you are making some tool calls with your model.
So, you know that…
Many models, they support this
kind of JSON generation, right?
I… I am sending the file again, but you can also find it in Discord.
Folks?
Here.
And what we are going to use here is YFinance.
And I'm writing a simple function here.
It is getStockFundamentals.
where I need to pass in a ticker.
Anybody knows what a ticker is?
Ticker is the stock symbol.
For example, for NVIDIA, it is NVDA. For Google, it is
G-O-O-G-L.
So, you just need to…
pass, like, those…
ticker here, and then internally, it is going to use this Wi-Finance library.
To get the stock information,
And respond with a JSON.
Okay.
If you see, we have added this tool decorator here, which we are importing from Langchain.
This tool decorator will register this function as an LLM tool.
Okay? This tool decorator, it will…
register this function that we have created in Python as an LLM tool.
that Langchain can use.
So, you can see here that apart from specifying the function name,
Uh, the function name?
The argument that it will take, and the kind of response it will generate.
I have also put in an effort to write
This doc string.
Do you know what… what is the use of this… this docstring?
Anyone in the chat?
Can you tell me what is the use of this docstring?
Yeah. Exactly. So…
Earlier, it was a good habit to write doc strings so that your fellow developer who's working with you, your colleagues can understand your code, right?
now those colleagues are LMs. So now, LLMs should be able to understand
what this particular function is supposed to do.
what it is taking as input, what it is providing as output,
So that it can call that tool and…
Use it to perform any kind of actions, okay? Here, what is the action? We have not defined any action yet. We are just defining the tool.
Here. Okay?
So, once you have all of these things ready,
So even if you have some legacy function in your code that you want to give to LLM, all you need to do
is documented well.
documenting it well-meaning means?
You add…
these pipends.
And after adding the typing hints, add a description.
After adding the description, you just use.
blank, uh, blankchain.tools.
And this tool decorator, decorate that function.
And that will be registered as a tool.
Now, after… after doing that,
You can take the LLM instance that you created. This LLM is this…
Chad Grock LLM, by the way, that we just created here. Okay, you can see LLM is equal to ChadGraw.
Langchain provides you a function.
Through which you can provide tools to LLM.
Okay? Here, we are using this bindTools function.
And you can pass in a list of tools,
So here, I have only one tool in the list, which is…
GetStop Fundamentals.
After I pass this, do you know what will happen internally? Can anybody guess what will happen internally?
How is Langchain going to use this tool?
With this LLM, what does this bind to?
Function 2.
No. Uh, I warned you guys, do not use any kind of jargons here, okay?
Right now, MCPs are jargon for us. We are not going to use MCP.
As a jargon in this particular lecture, okay? In, let's say, future some sessions, we may use it.
All right.
Folks, I will… I will give you some tip, okay?
Something that I have used personally for very effective learning
Do you all want to know the… see, I
I have had a very successful career
And I can learn things very fast. Do you want to know that one tip from me?
Yes
You want to know, like, how fast I personally learn things
Okay, so I'm gonna tell you the tip, but please follow it, okay? Because I'm not sharing this for free. I expect that you follow it.
When you are learning a given topic
Only and only focus on the core
Core, which is the herd. Say somebody was asking question, what is max retries? Somebody else asked the question
What is Harness AI
See, these are off-topics, folks
We will cover it. Don't worry, we'll cover it. And if you want to know more about max literatureize, you can Google it. Somebody say, okay, why finance? Does it cover Indian stocks?
That's not important for you to know
What is important for you to know is how LLM calls tools
How Agentic behavior works
How does LLM processes the output which tools are generating?
You should be hyper-focused on that, okay?
It's like
It's like, see, I do cooking, okay, so it's like I'm making a biryani
and I'm cutting vegetables when I'm cutting vegetables, I don't need to worry about garnishing, or I don't need to worry, worry about some later step.
Later step, you can do later on
Right now, you should be like, Arjun, you know, have you heard this story of Arjun where the guru of Arjun asked him question, okay, what do you see? He sees only the eye
So when Siddhant is explaining this tool augmented calling and if you're distracted on, okay, what this argument is doing, what that is doing, what's going to happen is you are going to miss the core of the concept
Okay, in my career
Throughout my career, this is what I have done. And see, if you are having a question, it is okay actually as a human, we all are curious. I also get a lot of curiosity, like, okay, what is this argument? What is that thing doing?
But
If you can restrain your curiosity and if you just focus on what is being taught
Later on, okay, later on you can quench the thirst of your curiosity. We will have Q&A session
But if you are eager to get answers of all your questions, see, you're going to miss out on the core, okay? Say I'm telling you folks, this is a real advice, something that has worked beautifully for me throughout my career.
I'm just sharing it with you, up to you, if you want to follow it or not, we will still answer all your questions. I'm not discouraging you to ask a question, but please, my sincere request, okay, focus on the core, because in the past this has happened is
We are explaining some core concept. People are wondering here and there, and later on they ask very basic question on the core concept
Why? Because their mind was not paying attention. You're not paying attention to the core concept that is being taught
Yeah. Okay.
Yeah? All right, go ahead. Thank you.
So, uh, we have registered this as tools.
And then we are using this bind tool to bind
This particular tool with this LLM.
What it is internally doing is…
It is taking out the name of the tool, taking out the description,
And whatever parameters and output that it gives.
And it is creating a system prompt with it.
And it is saying the LLM that you have access to all of these tools, use them when needed.
There, it will add this getStop Fundamental tool.
So now, when I call this particular
message here. When we invoke this LLM with a message, it is going to try to
Access these tools. You can ask
what is… how is NVIDIA performing right now, okay?
So…
Code basics is not a registered company, that is why you won't find anything for that.
But let's try with NVIDIA.
How is…
Just… call this, okay?
Once you call this, you will see…
that everything that you need to know about Nvidia,
Uh, so the actual content, the actual tool call that the LLM generates,
It will generate some kind of a…
JSON for it. So it will generate
This kind of a JSON.
And it will be an AI message.
Can… can you guys run it and share the output?
in chat.
So, LLMs, uh, good question, Adity. How is it converting it into ticker?
So, LLMs know enough that Nvidia has this particular
stock symbol, okay?
So, internally, they know, like,
all the popular stock symbols that are present in the market.
they're able to calculate it. And here you can see…
that somebody asked about Airtel.
And they got about… they got…
Airtel, but Airtel is… is…
Not a stock symbol. They did not get it for Airtel.
Uh, somebody asked it for AAC, I don't know what it is, but many people got the answer for Nvidia.
And you can see, it has responded with whatever Y-Finance generates.
Right? Whatever the tool responds with,
You get it there. So you get the price, you get the P-E ratio, you get the market cap, revenue growth,
What is the 52-week high? What is the 52-week low?
So, what we created just
Now, is a tool augmented LLM.
Okay? What did we create here? We created a tool augmented LLM.
Is it an agent?
Folks, tell me.
what we have created here, is it an agent?
No? Why? Why is it not an agent?
Yeah, do you know what is missing here?
Do you know what is missing?
Agency is missing, right? So…
This is the paper on which, like, most agents are based on. This is called React.
Which stands for Reasoning and Action. You saw that loop that I'll be sharing the slide, right? So, React loops can perform action.
if anybody wants to read this paper, you can go ahead and read this paper. This is
Written by interns at Google.
Okay. Can you believe it? It… like, this paper was written by interns at Google, and…
Most agent frameworks, they use this.
And uh… we are going to implement our React agent. Let's see how it works internally.
Okay?
So, we are going to build a finance research analyst agent that can query stock fundamentals, it can search through web,
And it can reason, okay? It can use reasoning.
To help us choose the right stock for us.
So, Langchain provides us with a createAgent function.
And we are going to use this createAgent function.
To build our agent. Internally, this createAgent function
is going to build this React loop.
What happens in this React loop? We have an LLM.
The LLM,
has some kind of tools.
that it has access to. And whenever we send in any message, the LLM
will reason around the goal that we have given it, and based on that goal that it has,
It will try to call
the tools that are available to it.
It will see what output those tools give it.
It will assess those outputs, and after evaluating those outputs,
It will decide whether it needs to call the tool again, or not.
In the end, after it has sufficient information, after it has
performed enough amount of actions to achieve that goal.
it will send out the response.
Okay? So, this is not a chain of thought, by the way, Gautam, this is not…
chain of thought reasoning. Uh, chain of thought reasoning happens internally in the LLM.
This is a React loop, okay? So LLM is reasoning.
And it is acting. And it is doing it in a loop.
So, that is why it is called React.
So, reason? Reasoning, and action.
Both of these happen together in an AI agent.
Okay? So what actions should I… should our agent be able to take?
It should search Google News and YFinance.
It should search the WiFinance API to get fundamentals, stock fundamentals.
So, understand, this is Yahoo News, and this is the YFinance API.
The tool that we just built is using YFinance API to only get the stock fundamentals, okay?
In the news, you will get various things like…
Uh, like, Nvidia is going to buy Hugging Face, some news like this.
Okay? And…
After that, we have…
provided you need access to Wikipedia as well, just in case it wants to know about something. Just in case it wants to search.
what, uh, is the stock symbol for Nvidia, or any other information regarding it?
So, how does it know
to come out of loop, it…
knows how to come out of a loop based on the goal that we have provided it, okay?
So, we can control a lot of things. We can control
the maximum number of iterations it can take.
And apart from controlling, like, apart from us controlling it,
It also… the LLM is smart enough
As soon as the LLM stops calling any tools,
Uh, it exits out of loop, and it generates the final response.
Okay?
Gaurav, please have patience, I'll tell you.
God have just answered me one thing.
Did your code run without an API key?
for Wi-Finance?
Did it run without any API key?
Yeah, then do you really need an API key?
No, right? It's, it's…
Just… just have patience. If…
If you… because why finance is just Google Y Finance, okay? Just Google Y Finance. What is it?
Just Google it. Huh? Why finance offers a Pythonic way to fetch financial market data from
It's an open-source tool, uses…
Yahoo's publicly available APIs, which has a free limit.
Okay? You get free stock codes.
just doing this one Google search can…
answer a very simple question that you have.
Uh, if, if…
You are able to run it without any API key. If you need any API key, I'll tell you. You see, I have all of these things open with me.
Yeah.
Alright, how did it find Google Nvidia company name?
In this, how is Google doing? So, Nitesh,
These LLMs are trained on large chunk of data. And because they are trained on such large chunk of data,
Uh, what happens is…
They have some intrinsic knowledge built on.
buildup. So…
You know that in that large chunk of data that has been scraped over the internet,
They already know that, okay, Google is a company, it has this particular stock price, they have seen a lot of texts
that contain these names and knowledge about them.
Okay, that's how they know. That's how ChatGPT, if you ask ChatGPT, just go to ChatGPT and ask.
What is Google? What is Nvidia? What are their stock symbols?
You'll be able to get it. Krishna is doing a great job answering questions.
Yes?
Uh… okay, Priya, yeah, thank you.
Yes. So, let's see.
We are now also going to install Wikipedia, which is, again, a Python library.
That helps us interact with Wikipedia API for free, without creating any API keys.
Okay? So we are going to use a Wikipedia, and we are also going to use SERP API.
Now, SERP API is a tool that allows us to
To perform Google search, and for this, we need to create an API key.
I have mentioned the steps here to create SOAR APIQ, okay?
So you need to go to Serve API… serveapapi.com,
And after going to SirPier.com,
You can go to the dashboard, create an API key,
copy it, and paste it here.
Just give me a thumbs up once you are done with this.
You need to have this SERP API key.
What we are going to do now is we have an LLM, we are just going to…
create more tools to provide it to our LLM.
And then… get started, okay?
So, folks, give me a thumbs up if you have created some API key. Once I see, like, majority of people have done it.
I will move forward.
Okay.
Alright, I see most people have created.
So, after we have our API keys and everything,
I'm just providing the SERP endpoint.
As they have suggested. And after that, I'm using the request library
to query news.
from Google, okay? So I'm going to use Google as the search engine, and I'm going to query all the news,
And I'm going to query it for the past 24 hours. So, whatever news
Related to NVIDIA has come up in past 24 hours,
It will fetch those news. You can play around with these parameters if you have any doubt of how to tune this parameter.
You have Serve API, you can go to the documentation of SERP API, or you can use
ChatGPT or Claude to ask how to
Update your query based on the requirement that you have, okay?
So, we are going to use Request API.
With the search API endpoint.
And in this function, I've simply written the logic
of calling the SERP API, fetching all the results,
And, uh, showcasing them in form of a…
good paragraph, okay, as a context to our LLM.
And then, I have provided the doc string.
I have provided what it needs as input, what it will provide as output,
And I have annotated it with, at the rate,
tool, okay? After adding this decorator, what happens?
So, after we add these things as decorator, what happens? LLM will…
Uh, sorry, Langchain will register this.
as a tool, okay? We still need to bind it with the LLM, but now it has been registered in Langchain as a tool.
Okay? It has been added in line chains.
Our Langchain instances, tool registry.
Now, I'm again going to use WiFinance.
And I'm going to…
get news for this particular tickle. Whatever ticker I get, I'm fetching news for it.
And I'm similarly joining all the lines together.
And this is my simple logic that I've created to deal with Y-Finance API. So, whatever items I get, I'm just iterating over the items,
Um, and each item is a news, okay? Each item is a news. I'm iterating over the items, I'm getting…
the content, the title, all of those things.
I am concatenating them together.
as a line, and…
joining them together as a paragraph, okay?
That's all I'm doing. And in Wikipedia as well, I've created this function to search Wikipedia.
Here as well, we are using the Wikipedia library to search.
some query. We are fetching the top 3 results. After fetching the top 3 results, we are just…
Fetching the Wikipedia summaries.
And we are, uh…
creating our document with that.
Once we have done all of these, and we have annotated all of the tools that we have,
With at the rate tool,
I'm going to create a list of tools.
that I can provide to my LLM here. So you can see,
I've created a tools list where I've added all of these tools.
And I've also mentioned in the comment what each of these tools do.
So, now I have my list of tools, I've just printed to see, like, what all they take.
Uh, like, what is the name?
what do they expect as an input? What do they provide as an output?
All of those things. And then…
My tools are ready.
All I need to do now is…
create, uh, like, use this createAgent function to build our agents.
Okay? And uh…
whatever functions you add here, you need to annotate them.
with this tool decorator, okay?
If you annotate them with this tool decorator, then only LandChain will be able to parse them.
And get all this information, and register them in the registry.
Alright? So…
We have used this createAgent function,
And in this createEgent function, I will pass the following system prompt, okay?
Uh, earlier we used very simple system prompt, but this is what a typical system prompt would look like.
So, folks, let's read the system prompt and understand this is important.
So please focus here.
I have mentioned… so, in the first two lines,
I have given this…
agent or personality. I've said it, that you are Finbot.
An export equity research analyst, okay?
Then, I'm specifying some task.
that it needs to follow, uh, that it needs to achieve.
After specifying the task,
I'm setting some ground rules.
for this particular agent. And then,
I'm specifying the output format.
Okay? So, there is a format structure called
craft prompt. Craft prompt starts, uh, like, stands for…
C is for context.
R is for role, A is for, uh, I think…
action, and F is for format.
And, yeah, T is for…
I think, task, okay? So…
like, all of these, uh…
Acronyms mean only one thing. You need to provide
your agent enough context, you need to give it some role, so that it is in that role, and it
acts as the role that we have given it.
You need to set some ground rules.
And then you need to specify the task very clearly, you need to specify the output format very clearly.
Okay, this is what a typical system prompt for an agent would look like.
Many agents, like, this is a simple agent, so it is very simple. Many agent can have a very elaborate system prompt as well.
But this is a basic one that we have created.
So, we have our tools, we have… we have our LLM instance.
And we have imported this.
create agent function from LandChain.
We can use this function, I'm calling it my finance agent,
And I'm using the createAgent function.
Passing in my LLM, my list of tools,
So, my list of annotated tools here, all of these 4 tools.
And my system prompt here.
Once I do this, my agent is ready.
Okay? Internally, it is implementing the React loop that we
So, earlier, we are going to see how to implement this React loop from scratch in Langraph.
in, like, uh…
In the session next week. But right now, just, just…
see how it is created using Langchain.
After that,
I can use the invoke
method of my agent.
And passing the actual instruction to follow.
Which is, give me a quick analyst brief on Nvidia.
Is now a good time to buy?
I've printed the agent trace here to show you what all it does.
So you see that it received a human message.
After receiving a human message,
It will make a call,
to the tool.
You can see after it has made the tool call,
It is receiving a tool message,
Okay? This tool message is what?
You guys remember, right, when we discussed about Langchain, I told about the four different types of messages.
Can anyone name all the four different types of messages?
System message, human message, AI message, and tool message. Correct. So, see.
We have human message, we have AI message, system message is something that is happening internally.
In langchain. And then we have the tool message. We again have, like, AI message.
tool message. So, you see, it is… it is not calling a single tool, and we have only specified our goal.
Okay, we have only specified our goal.
And based on this goal, it is iterating through
this, like, it is iterating through this loop of…
Reasoning and action.
multiple times to come up with the final response. You can see,
that in this invoke function, there are multiple
There is only one human message.
There are multiple AI messages and multiple tool messages.
Okay, after all the AI message and tool message, you will see that
The final response will look something like this.
And this response is
following the same structure that we provided in our system prompt, which is…
Here. Okay?
Now, if I want this agent to respond with…
JSON of this response?
what do I need to do? Any idea, folks?
This is… this is your homework. Just…
Just try to…
generate this response in a JSON format.
Okay. I want all of you to run this with the company of your choice, and…
Share the responses here.
Folks, run this code and share the response field, okay?
Okay, I see Dell, I see…
I think it is Pfizer.
PFA's Pfizer.
All right, we see NVIDIA.
TCS, AMD,
And you can see, right, it is… it is a very good… it is a tool that you can use.
You can, uh…
and analyze any stock.
And get recommendation, you can do these things.
So, let's…
Let's wait a while for people to answer.
All right.
Rajfan, you need to press Enter after…
Having the Grok API key, okay?
After pasting the Grok API key, you need to press Enter.
Otherwise, it will keep spinning.
Okay, folks, congratulations. You have just built your own agent.
That is, doing market analysis for you and generating a report.
Okay?
Now…
Tell me…
Now you know how to build agents using Langchain.
Okay, very simple agent you can build using LangChain. Tell me what are you going to build.
I will do a recap in the end.
Okay. Tell me what are you going to build with the knowledge that you have gained.
Okay, Bharat is going to build an AI news agent.
It's okay, I'll, like, post something that you built on Discord.
I would love to see you guys building some…
agents, okay?
All right, folks.
Now…
Let me go through it once again.
Very briefly, so we created our tools.
Tools are nothing but Python functions.
With docstring, with documentation.
annotated with this add the rate tool.
And after this,
We used the createAgent function,
from Langchain, we defined a system prompt,
We used the createAgent function from Langchain, we passed in our LLM, we passed in our tools, and we passed in the system prompt.
to create our agent.
And then we use the agent.invoke function.
Passed in our message, the agent went through this React loop,
Okay? The agent went through…
This React loop internally.
By calling tools, checking what their tools responded with, calling the tools again, reasoning around the output,
Doing this loop again and again, and then coming out with an output.
And after doing all of this, we are able to build our finance agent.
But something is missing here, okay? What is missing? Let's…
seat in this particular cell, right below.
The cell will, uh, which you just ran,
You can see, I have sent a message saying, now compare it with Nvidia.
Okay? I have asked it.
Now, compare it with NVIDIA.
And when I say, now compare it with Nvidia,
what is happening here?
You can see it is just giving me a stock analysis of AMD.
Sorry, now compare it with AMD, it is just giving me a stock analysis of AMD.
It has not mentioned Nvidia specifically anywhere, okay? It has mentioned it here, but it has also mentioned some other company.
What does this tell us?
What does this kind of response tell us? We have asked it that we need a comparison between
something that we asked before, we asked it to generate a report for NVIDIA.
We asked it now, compare it with AMD, but it has only provided us
with details of AMD. So, what is missing here?
Exactly, right? So…
on their own,
When you use this invoke function,
Each… each session that is going, it is stateless, okay? It is not…
the agent is not saving the state,
of all the past messages that you have sent it.
Unless you add some kind of a memory layer to it, okay?
So, we are going to add memory into our agent.
And after adding the memory,
Uh, you will see that it will be able to answer such follow-up questions, okay? Right now, it is not able to answer any follow-up questions.
Every… every request that we give to it is an isolated request in itself.
Okay?
Yes, Shrikant, congratulations, Srikant has generated a JSON. Well done. Srikant also post how you generate the JSON.
And share a screenshot of the code that you wrote for it.
Uh, in SERP API is giving phone number mandatories.
I think in India, it is mandatory.
It was not the case, like, few months ago, but now they have introduced it.
Because many people are using it for free, they are creating multiple accounts,
Using different emails, they want to restrict it, maybe, that.
So you can pass in… if you can provide your phone number if you want to use it.
Okay, if you do not want to use SERP API, you can use some other search library, like Tablei or something else.
And uh… yeah, Krishna is…
Yeah, kudos to Krishna for supporting everybody.
All right. So, now…
Uh, we saw that the missing part was memory.
And we're going to add memory to our agent.
There are two types of memory.
that is provided by Langchain. One is short-term memory,
And another is long-term memory.
Let's see what is the difference here.
Short-term memory is for individual chat sessions.
Can any… can anybody tell me what an individual chat session is… what an individual chat session looks like?
You all use ChatGPT or Cloud, right?
In ChatGPT, when you click on a new message,
Right? When you click on a new message, you are taken to a blank window.
That… that ChatGPT window is like a one… is like one session.
So, all the messages that you…
share, it will have context on that.
But when you open up a new chat window and ask something related to the previous chat window that you opened,
ChatGPT won't be able to answer it, okay?
Why? Because that memory is short-term memory.
It is preserved in one…
Uh, session. One session of…
AI and human, okay? So you can see it.
Short-time memory works on a single session,
With whose messages?
can look like this. A human message, an AI message,
A human message, an AI message, some tool…
some tool messages in between, like this, okay?
But have you…
used the memory function of Claude.
And… or ChatGPT.
And you see that when you tell something
To charge GPT to remember, specifically, it will use a tool, and it will say that memory is updated.
And then we're in a different session as well.
When you ask something about the previous session that you asked it to do,
It is going to remember it.
Yeah? What kind of memory is that?
What kind of memory is that?
Any idea what kind of memory is that?
It is long-term memory, yes.
So, long-term memory is memory that is persistent.
across different sessions, okay? Across different chart.
So, how can you specify, like, how can you know what is a session?
You see that when you use ChatGPT,
Char GPT, at the end, after chat, it will have a slug.
That slug is a UUID, right? That UUID is like the ID of that particular chat session.
Okay? And…
Our line chain memory will also work in a similar way.
So, we implement short-term memory using checkpointers, and we use long-term memory… we implement long-term memory using…
memory stores. We are going to look into short-term memory now.
And we are going to use this in-memory Saver.
But langchain provides us with different memory tools, so if you look for Langchain…
Memory, and…
You will see that it provides various providers, right?
Let me go to short-term memory.
And it… it comes up with various different providers.
Let me see integrations, maybe…
integrations for…
memory do we have?
Okay.
So you see short-term memory, it provides…
us, access to
this in-memory store, but apart from in-memory store, it also provides us access to Postgres, it provides access to MongoDB,
I think Redis is also there, yeah. Postgres, MongoDB, Redis, Oracle.
So, langchen provides all of these things out of the box.
Okay. And we are going to use the in-memory saver for the time being.
Okay? In the in-mem…
Uh, in our CreateAgent function, all we need to do is…
Add this check pointer.
And instantiate our memory store.
I give you homework of using SQLite Memory Saver.
Okay, escalate or Postgres, you can use any of those. But…
replace this in-memory saber with some persistent storage, okay?
take it as a homework.
Now…
All you need to provide there as well is
add this checkpointer parameter.
And provide the…
memory instance, if it is…
SQL or something else, just provide it there.
And… after you have done this,
Your memory is created.
Now, only thing that we need to change while invoking our agent is we need to pass this
config, uh, parameter. In this config parameter, which is a dictionary,
We need to pass in a thread ID, okay?
This thread ID is like the slug that you see at the end of ChatGPT.
You guys remember, right? Uh, when you use a new ChargeAPT chat, when you interact with it, you will see that ChatGPT will have something like ChatGPT.com slash chat slash
It will have some random UUID.
Yeah? Have you guys seen it? Give me a thumbs up if you have seen it in ChatGPT.
Right?
Yeah, so here, this thread ID is similar to that
UUID that you see in ChatGPT.
Okay? So… so if this thread ID is present,
In… while you are invoking,
your agent?
In config, then your agent will understand that, okay,
This particular person is asking me about this chat session.
So let me look at the past conversation in this particular chat session, and answer his question.
So here you can see, I have asked a similar question. I have provided this thread ID.
Use Alice Session 1, uh, anybody remembers Bob and Alice?
Do you guys remember Bob and Alice?
It's okay if you're too old to remember, but…
Uh, I hope you guys remember your computer network class from your engineering.
Yeah, classic example in crypto. Yeah, exactly.
So, guys, see.
I have given this message of, give me a quick brief of it, uh, Nvidia.
It has generated a, uh…
generated similar response.
Okay, I'm not printing the response, but here you can see in the end that NVIDIA analysis is present here.
You can print it just the way…
like, I printed it.
Uh, earlier?
And, uh, then…
You can see I have asked a follow-up question using the same config, okay? I've used the same config.
which has this particular same thread ID.
In the passing… by passing the same config, I have asked it, how does it compare to AMD on valuation?
And when you see here, I have not mentioned Nvidia or anything.
But from the previous charts, from its memory,
It knows that I'm talking about Nvidia.
Okay, earlier it did not know. Earlier, it just gave me an analysis of…
AMD. Now, it knows about Nvidia, and it has…
generated this.
particular comparison for me, okay? And this is
Using the same format that we had earlier,
Only thing is, the PE ratio and all those things are now
Uh, compared here.
Back to back, okay?
So, folks,
Now, I can ask another question with the same config, and you can see…
Given both, which is bet… which has better growth prospect, and it will say which has got, uh…
better growth prospect, it will…
show that NVIDIA shows stronger…
higher velocity growth. AMD's…
And this growth is solid, but comparatively slower, okay?
So, it has done all the comparisons as well.
So folks…
Uh, congratulations, you have built
your agent with memory. I'm quickly showing, like, how to create
an SQLite.
memory saver, right? Right? So, this…
Particular instance is, if you're running it locally,
Then, uh…
This particular memory is being stored
in memory, okay? So every time you…
run your code again, okay? The memory will be cleaned out.
With ChatGPT, uh, with Langraph, Checkpoint SQLite,
You can use this Escalade saver, and this will create a SQLite database for you.
And it will save all the chat information in that SQLite database, okay? Here as well, we are not doing anything, we are just…
creating an SQLite connection.
We are passing in that connection to our SQLite Saver instance.
as connection, okay?
After that, we are adding that
check pointer here in the agent.
Okay?
And our persistent agent is now created. You can run it similarly.
And you will see the same kind of response.
So folks, run until this, run until this point, install semantic router.
And give me a thumbs up if it is working out for you, okay?
Just run it. After that, we can take a break.
of 20 minutes. When we return from the break, we can talk about memory.
Oh, sorry, we can talk about routing.
Pawan, the agent is doing action,
It is making Google Search autonomously. It is
Uh, analyzing the stock autonomously, and in the end, it is generating a report for us.
Okay.
Now, if you add in
a mailing tool, okay? Try this. Add a Gmail tool, okay?
just write a Python function where you can pass in the
email ID, and pass in the message, and it will send a message to that particular email.
Uh, and add that email tool to your agent.
to your tool list.
And just ask it that…
Uh, just change the system prompt that as the, uh, that…
Send email to the user in the specified email ID.
And in your prompt, just…
Ask your question, and provide your email ID.
And you can see it will send you an email.
Okay, so it will be able to perform those kind of actions.
Here, the action is different. Here, the action is searching and preparing a report.
how React Loop comes to an end, we will… we will discuss about the internals of React Loop,
In our next session, okay?
Uh, when we built a React loop through.
Right now, just understand that when… when…
the tool calling ends. When the…
Agent understands that it has
completed, calling all the tools that it…
wanted to call. It will…
stop calling any tools and generate a final response. That's when the React group will end.
Okay? Whenever the agent stops,
making function calls at that time, React loop will end.
I'm still not convinced how it is an agent, as ChatGPT will also do this, but in the beginning, we called
that not an agent. We called the model inside ChatGPT not an agent.
We said that nowadays, ChatGPT is also agentic.
If you talk about ChatGPT, that was…
like, released the first version of ChatGPT that was released, the first few version of ChatGPT that was released.
It won't be able to search, make Google search, or do all those things, okay?
When it was provided with tools.
You know, after this React paper come out. Do you know when it came out? It came out in 2023.
So, in early 2023, you would have noticed that ChatGPT, yeah, see?
March 2023. So, in early 2023, you would have noticed that ChatGPT added the feature of tools.
like, added the feature of search, memory, all of those things.
When it did that, it became an agent.
Okay? When…
Now, agency also has levels. So, you can consider this as
Uh, degree 1…
agent. There are multiple layers of agent… agency, okay?
This is a very simple agent that we have built.
How can we know which session ID need to pass when we have list of questions and responses? Hararendra, how do you manage
sessions in any backend application.
So, folks, think like an engineer, okay?
Here, this session ID is just one component.
But imagine you're building an application like ChatGPT, where you have used
This createAgent function in the backend.
Now, every time a new user logs in, every time a new session is created from the UI,
You will create a new session ID, you will pass that session ID based on the state of your
Let's say you're using React. So based on the state of your React application, on what page is the user landing, okay?
If the user has landed on that particular page, you pass in that session ID in here in your agent.
Okay? So this is a…
An engineering decision that you will make.
Why are we even defining routes? We need to check.
Uh…
Let's talk about routing when we discuss about routing.
Is there something like glucose on continuously we need to manually break? Do we have something like break?
We have something like max iterations, okay? We can pass in max iteration.
to our agent. Uh, we can keep it, like,
do maximum number of… do…
10 iteration at maximum.
Uh, do not take an 11th iteration to answer my question.
How to create persistent memory per user?
Again, Ankit, I think my previous answer to Harendra…
answers that. Uh…
It is an engineering decision that you need to make, so you need to design your backend in such a way.
that, just like, you know, just like how you… let's say you are designing a social media application.
How do you design different charts? Or how do you design…
Uh, how do you assign, like, different posts?
a post ID, okay? Let's say you're building Facebook, how do you decide that, okay,
this particular post will have this post ID.
all the comments in this post will show up for this post itself, yeah?
Those things you can mention… you can manage in your backend.
In this layer, in the AI layer,
You only need to pass in that.
thread ID here, okay?
When we ask it about who has better growth prospect, why is it still…
Will it still call the tools?
And follow the format. Uh, I don't think it will… like, it really depends. It depends on the model that we are using, how that model was trained.
And what?
probabilistic choice that it made, uh, that it…
made at that point of time. But here, you can see that it had both the reports, it had the Nvidia report, it had the AMD report.
And it just compared both the reports.
It did not call any tools.
So, this also shows the agency. We are not saying…
our agent that called all these tools. We are just saying you have access to these tools.
Okay? Do whatever you need to do with these.
And achieve my goal.
So, it is deciding on its own whether it needs to call this tool, at what point of time it needs to call some tool,
All of that. We have not…
mentioned anywhere how that flow will go.
Okay? It is descending the flow on its own.
If an action can be performed by both tools, how will agents select
Which group? Uh…
This is something very common, and this is not a good practice, okay?
If an action can be performed with both tools, you need to specify.
that what that tool is good for in.
the doc string, okay?
And many times, like, here we have provided similar tools in form of search engines, right? So we also do the same. We also search on Google, we search on…
different websites, and then we come up with
our report. If we have to generate some kind of report like that.
So, same thing, it can use multiple tools, okay? It will check.
With Google, did it receive enough responses? No, it did not receive enough responses.
Let me use Yahoo.
It used to say explicitly that I cannot…
answer anything? Yeah, ChatGPT used to say this.
How to make agents stop, again, pass the max iter…
parameter here in the quarks, you'll be able to…
I will show you how to do that.
I run this, but not able to figure out how memory is working here.
Quick recap.
So, what memory is doing is…
When you pass this config here,
Then, it is checking, okay, the thread ID is same.
If the thread ID is same,
It is… just…
adding, uh… it is creating a, you know, table and adding all the messages.
with the thread ID to that table.
When you're asking some question, it is fetching from this
thread ID. It is fetching the messages from this thread ID.
And adding it in the system message.
to the LLM, okay?
No, by default, APIs do not have any browsing feature. So, that's what I'm telling you. Use ChatGPT, you will be able to do a lot of things, like…
browse news and everything. Use OpenAI API.
for GPT 5.3, any of the latest models, even the latest model.
Use the API. It will only generate text.
Okay, I see mostly Krishna has answered all the questions.
How the schema is decided?
Uh, schema is, like, inbuilt.
Because Langscreen is managing the schema for you.
You are not creating schema. Langchin is managing how…
Plankton is deciding how you need… how it needs to manage memory.
Okay. Any Python developers have used Celery here?
Celery, or anybody who has used Kafka or something like that.
Or key cloak. Anybody has used Key Cloak?
Okay? In all of these tools, you need to pass in some persistent
Maybe, right? For example, you pass Postgres to KeyCloak,
to store all the roles and information and all of those things.
Do you specify the schema and everything? No, right? Key Clock takes care of it. Key Clock will create the schema,
for how it needs to manage everything internally.
Similarly, langchen is also creating its own schema.
You just need to pass in the…
DB connection, okay? Same for Celery as well. In Celery, you need to provide
Redis or something, and it will create, like, all the internal things.
On its own.
But at this, the agent will get confused.
Many… and it depends on the model that you're using, okay? Simple models will get confused.
And if you're using a very smart model, like Claude or something,
Claude can figure it out.
based on the tool name, based on the input and output, it can figure it out.
Yeah, it is still session level, short-term, uh…
Sarat, we will, uh…
We will discuss about long-term memory later on, okay?
Just experiment with short-term right now.
We will experiment with long-term memory later on.
Alright, folks, I hope you had a good time, you learned about agents.
We will talk about, uh…
semantic routing later on, which is an essential topic.
And, uh,
Let's take a break for 20 minutes now.
Krishna, can we start?
Uh, timer for 20 minutes?
No, we are not going to talk about long-term memory today.
Let's talk about layout. We are going to talk about it.
In one of the coming sessions. I don't want to overwhelm you with a lot of things, okay?
You have just built your agent, focus on it.
By the way, I'll tell you something. Like, Code Basics has created its own agent library, just like Langchain.
So, let me share a link for that.
Sandeep, when did we say that today's session is about?
RAG.
No, today was always about agents, like…
In RAG, we do not have anything left over, right?
Yeah, uh, Atishai. Atishai built…
a project? Yeah, so today we will give you assignment regarding RAC.
Uh, Sanjee, if I can understand, but…
This is something, like, that you have to…
You know, you have to find a way. You have to build a schedule such that it allows you the time to…
follow up with those things, and…
you know, spend time absorbing the topics and building it.
push you're on the right track. That's how we do it.
So, we create one…
Uh, we create one embedding.
One query embedding, and that query embedding is used by all the others.
Okay? Uh…
It is used by… it is used to…
query all the three different
um, vector stores that we have.
And uh… yeah, that's…
We fetch all the data, and we stuff it in the prompt.
Folks, it's okay. Like, SERP API, if you missed it, it's okay, don't worry.
I will give a quick overview in the end. Okay, I can give a quick overview in the end.
And you can create swerve API and learn it later on.
Rakapon, can you ask…
In Discord, you will get help.
Ankit, I explained, like, multiple times, uh…
taking time for each of the core snippets.
Um, can you… can you ex… like…
tell me exactly where I was fast, and…
where I need to slow down, so I'll take care of it.
like, uh, very fast. Let me just revise everything once.
And…
Let's go over it again.
So, we are going to use Langchain.
Langchengrok and Langgraph.
We…
Added our Grok API key. Just remember, after adding the API key, you need to press Enter. If you do not press Enter, this will just…
go on and on.
We created the chat… we used ChadGrock to create an instance of our JPTO SS LLM.
And then…
We use the YFinance library,
To get stock fundamentals, we created this function, we annotated it with addTheRate tool,
When we add any description here,
All of those things are registered by Langchain.
And when we use bind tool to add
these functions as tools. These go into this system prompt,
Uh, sorry, these docstring, the stock, uh, the function name, all of those things, they go into the…
System prompt of LLM.
And it is able to call tools like these.
Okay. After that, we used…
create React, uh…
Sorry, we used createAgent function.
to build a React agent. What happens in a React agent is, it is an LLM.
with multiple tools.
Such that it can reason around the task that it needs to perform.
And calls the tools based on that.
Once it has concluded executing all the tools that it needed to, and it has enough information,
It comes out of this loop,
And it generates a final response for us.
So, we built an agent using Wikipedia, SERP API,
and Yahoo Finance APIs.
We use the same method, we defined a function, wrote the core logic,
that needs to be executed in that function. Defined our…
doc string for each of those functions, and annotated them with
At the rate tool decorator.
Once we did that, we used the createAgent function
Uh, from Langchain.
We defined our system prompt, and we added all of these things, like our LLM, all the tools, list of all the tools that we created,
And our system prompt.
to this function to create our agent.
We call this agent, and we saw that the message was printed successfully.
But when we asked a follow-up question, we saw that the LLM did not remember what we had asked it earlier, and it only answered based on
the new message that we sent.
That was because we missed to add memory.
So, we learned about memory.
Blankchain has two different types of memory.
Short-term memory, and long-term memory.
Short-term memory is a memory that persists across, like,
that persists across different messages in a session, okay? So, across different messages.
in one particular session, it is like the ChatGPT chat window that you open.
Long-term memory is like the memory that ChatGPT or something.
other AI platform that you use, they remember it.
Okay?
So, long-term memory?
is memory that acts
across different sessions that we have, okay?
So, it can act across?
different chat windows.
We used in-memory Saver first.
to create an in-memory
check pointer. We just added this checkpointer param, and…
instantiated the in-memory saver.
to add memory to our agent.
One thing that becomes compulsory with this is
Providing the config with a thread ID.
So, we did that.
We provided the config with threadID.
Each thread ID?
corresponds to different sessions that you want to create, okay?
So if the thread ID is same, LLM will assume that you're asking questions for the same
session, or in the same chat window.
And we ran our experiment again with follow-up questions, and we were able to see that
Our agent remembered everything.
We migrated from in-memory Saver to SQLite.
checkpointer, and…
Using Escalade Saber, we were able to persist
these messages in an SQLite database, okay?
which is financeagent.deb.
Uh, we ran the same experiment, and it wa- it worked in the similar fashion.
Okay? So that is all that we did today.
I hope for anybody who had missed it,
Uh, like…
was homestead because of SERPI or anything, was able to understand this.
Let's move on to…
Understanding what our outer is.
Okay. So, folks, tell me,
What do you understand from the word router?
Okay, I see most of you are answering it correctly.
So, you remember, right, in HTTP as well, we have different routes.
So we have path parameter, which tells us, like, which route.
To go to, right?
So, router is something that lets us decide
which path we need to take.
Okay? This… this image…
Uh, reminds me of a poem.
the road not taken, I don't know if you guys remember it.
Uh, so…
Browder is something that, uh…
tells us which path to take.
So let's understand it with an example. So, what is the use of router in AI?
you might be thinking. So, let's say…
Uh, let's assume that this is MakeMyTrape, or some similar application like that, or this is BookMyShow.
And we ask it a question, how do I change seat in my flight from Delhi to New York?
Now, when it goes to LLM,
There can be multiple agent…
that deal with, uh, you know, different kind of…
queries. So…
You have a new booking, you have existing booking, you have tech support.
Now, the LLM needs to decide first.
that… which workflow should I send it to? Because…
Each of these will have their own separate, different workflows, right?
The new booking workflow might have something.
Where you need to register the user.
You need to ask them about the flight details and everything from scratch, create a new… create a booking.
So, create a new row in the table, something like that.
If some… if you have some query regarding existing booking, you may need to read an existing record from a table.
And you need to update something.
Uh, regarding a specific record, okay? Like here.
Here, the person wants to change…
seat in the flight from Delhi to New York. So it will be…
an existing booking, okay?
So, from this message,
Can you identify which one to choose?
Can you, as a human, identify?
which particular route to choose?
just using this message.
Yeah? Existing, exactly.
We need to use the existing booking route.
Now, it's easy for us.
We understand this text.
Okay. And…
Routing your application was very easy when we built traditional applications.
traditional web applications, Android applications, all of those things, because
There, user actually told us their intent by clicking on the buttons.
Okay? They told us the intent.
By clicking on the buttons, it was very algorithmic.
If I'm using any app, let's say if I'm using Facebook,
And I have used… I've not used Facebook or Instagram, like, in…
it's been a decade since I've used them, but I don't know how they work, but let's say…
If I have to go from timeline to messages.
Then, I'm clicking the message button. That's how I… I mean, I'm being taken to route.
Okay, the message route.
But in AI application,
How do you identify which route to go to?
It is not algorithmic.
Right? So, any ideas? How can we…
route users' queries.
to, you know, different…
different routes.
Exactly. So it is semantic-based, yeah? Based on the semantic meaning of the query.
And we try to identify the intent of the user.
based on the…
semantic meaning of their query.
Alright? So, this particular type of routing is called intent-based routing,
Or, it is also known as semantic routing.
Okay? It is called intent-based routing, or semantic routing.
We see the message that the user has sent,
We try to use an embedding model
To understand the semantic
Meaning of that particular sentence, and then we classify
Uh, that particular sentence into…
some of the existing intents that we have with us.
Okay? So, how does it work?
you send any user query,
There is a route classifier.
And, uh,
let's say, like, this is another use case, okay?
You send any user query, there is a route classifier.
And based on, like, the query that you have asked,
It can choose whether it is simple, it is a doc lookup, or it is some kind of complex workflow.
So, we built a rack pipeline, right, yesterday?
Yesterday, we built…
RAC pipeline, and we actually built two different rack pipelines. We built one,
For answering FAQ questions.
from our FAQ sheet,
And from the document that we had, from the PDF document. But we also built another
rack pipeline.
That was our SQL rack pipeline.
You guys remember it, right? We had SQL rack?
So we… yeah, hybrid and SQL.
Now, how do we decide
which rack pipeline to call based on user's question?
How do we decide which
which rack pipeline to call.
Okay, we can use some kind of a…
Intent Classifier, or a semantic router, right?
We can use some kind of an intent classifier or a semantic router.
You can use LLMs to predict the route, okay? You can use LLM to classify those routes.
But should you use LLMs to classify this route?
Don't you think it could be expensive?
Yeah?
Yes, it is expensive, right? Using LLM for
Classifying routes could be expensive, because
you are spending tokens for it. You are spending… you are going to spend tokens. Tokens equals…
some cents, or some dollars.
All right? So, that could be difficult.
Uh, and uh…
Another way is we use
An embedding model, okay?
And we create cluster.
of these routes. Like, simple doc lookup, complex. We create clusters of these routes,
And, uh, whichever…
A document is fetched the most.
based on our query, we say that it
our query belongs to that particular route.
Okay? I will explain how this happens in detail when we code, but let's look at this architecture, okay?
This is called model routing, or workflow routing, okay? So, you have a router,
you identify which particular model you need to go to, or which particular
Pipeline you need to execute. And this is…
a very standard architecture, yes.
So, Gotham, yeah, this is a very standard architecture that is being used these days.
Okay? You do not want to use
a powerful model for each and every question that you have, okay?
Uh, how many of you have used coding agents, like cursor…
For anti-gravity, something like that.
or kiro.
Any coding agents you have used?
You know, there is an auto mode.
Where, uh, the coding agent itself decides which model to use based on the task that you get.
Give it, yeah? There as well, semantic routing is used.
Okay? That is also doing this.
route classification.
Okay?
So, let's…
look into this. Let's see how…
Uh, we can implement semantic router.
Okay? So, here, the example that I showed you is complexity-based routing.
Okay? The earlier example was intent-based routing. Here, we are saying,
Uh, something called complexity-based routing, and this is used in coding agents a lot.
And we are going to use a library called Semantic Router.
It is a super-fast library. It uses embedding models rather than LLMs.
It will not cost us any tokens.
It is going to use the same embedding model that we used earlier to generate our embeddings or something like that.
And it provides a framework.
to use those embedding models,
To do this clustering of routes,
And then, identify.
Uh, which route the user is asking to choose.
Okay, so we are going to understand semantic router and
this routing, using
coding examples.
Let's get started, okay? Semantic Router…
is very popular. It is being used
by a lot of different companies, it has a lot of, like, GitHub stars.
Uh, and I have used it in many production applications.
So yeah, I can say that it is an industry standard.
Okay?
So, let's see how we are going to do this.
I'm going to share my screen. You have the same notebook, okay? We are going to use the same notebook.
When you scroll below, you will see…
that, uh, this particular line written, install semantic router. Come to this line, give me a thumbs up once you are here.
Yeah, you all are here. So, we are going to install this semantic router. It is an open source library, so you can…
Google, uh, semantic router as well.
After it is installed, let's see how it works, okay?
So, semantic router, internally, will store embeddings of different routes.
Okay? So let's say you have Route 1, Route 2, Route 3. You will provide example.
of what a query in Route 1 may look like, what a query in Route 2 may look like, what a query in Route 3 may look like.
Semantic Router will take all the examples from each route, create embeddings, and store them in a vector store.
Now, as soon as user asks any question to Symantec Router,
It will fetch, let's say, 5 different embeddings, okay?
And out of the 5 embeddings it fetched,
Let's say 2 embeddings,
Where from?
Route 1, 3 embeddings were from Route 2.
Then, what could be the route that the user has asked for?
Any ideas? So, after the user asked a query,
Two embeddings were fetched from Route 1.
And 3 embeddings were fetched from Route 2.
Yeah? Route 2, exactly. How were you able to identify it? Because?
The query that the user asked was more relevant
to Route 2, right?
It was more relevant to Route 2, that's why more embeddings came from Route 2.
So, this is the simple logic that semantic router uses.
And this is how, like, we implement it.
So, let's say I have used
Uh, you need to import.
the route class from semantic router.
Then you will need to import the semantic router itself.
And you also need to import an encoder.
Now, we are using Hugging Face Encoder. Any idea why we need an encoder?
Any idea why we need an encoder?
Exactly. For embedding.
Right? For finding the…
for creating the embedding. So here, we have used a slightly better model, which is Quenembedding 0.6B.
So, we are using this Quinn embedding model.
And I have passed in this embedding model name to my Hugging Face encoder.
And you can see it will load it, and this is the standard procedure that you have seen until
Now, for embedding modules, okay?
After this, the crucial part comes.
I'm importing this route class.
And I'm instantiating it.
with two different parameters that it takes.
First is the name of this route.
What is the name of this route? It is…
stock analysis. So…
I can add all my stock analysis-related questions here, like what is Apple's PE ratio, show me Tesla's market cap, what are Nvidia's earnings per share.
How much revenue did Microsoft make last year? So,
how well my router works depends on the kind of examples I've provided here, okay?
It will depend on the kind of examples that I've provided here.
So I've created this talk analysis route. Similarly, I've also created this market news route.
Provided. Few examples here.
And then, I have created a general finance route.
provided some more examples here.
And with this,
I am going to instantiate my semantic router.
Okay? So you see, I have created…
these routes, these three routes,
with examples and their name. Okay, these are the only two essential things that we need to pass here.
Internally, semantic router will create embeddings for each of these.
as a single chunk, right?
And then it will store all of these
Examples in a vector store.
So, that will happen when we…
instantiate it here using Semantic Router, okay? So, let's see.
I have specified all my routes, like stock analysis route,
market news route, general finance route,
And provided it as a list of routes.
After that, I have instantiated my semantic router.
by providing it the encoder,
You know, you all remember the encoder, right? This is the…
Hugging Face Encoder.
And then I've provided some…
The list of routes that I've created here, okay?
And AutoSync local means that it will store all of these locally in the memory.
Otherwise, what will happen? Every time my application starts, if I do not have this,
Every time my application starts, it will…
regenerate the embeddings.
Okay, it will regenerate the embeddings, it will store all of it in memory.
So if the application restarts, then it will take a lot of time, because routing will…
restart.
Okay? Once I have done this, my route… my router is created.
Are you all following me?
Are you all able to understand how we created our routes?
Yeah. Okay.
Explain locally means C. When I say auto-sync Local, it means that
Uh, it will store all the embeddings,
It will store all the embeddings,
Locally in some folder.
Okay? Otherwise, what will happen?
This semantic router will be in memory.
So, every time my application starts,
It is going to…
Um, every time, like, the application starts,
It will… it is going to use the encoder and
create embeddings, new embeddings, every time the application starts, because
And store it in memory itself.
So, when you close your application, all the embeddings that were created are gone.
Okay? When you restart the application, they will be generated again.
So, to avoid that, to…
like, keep the startup time…
Less, we are going to use this.
Autosync Local.
Semantic Router right now is not using any VectorDB, but you can connect it with a VectorDB.
I will… I will discuss about those things.
In a while, okay? Just give me some time, I'll discuss it in while.
So, that's how you create your own.
routes, and…
Let's test it with a few queries.
Okay? So what is Apple's current P-E ratio?
When I asked about this, it told me that it is general finance, which is wrong.
Uh, tell me about the latest…
FedRate decision, okay?
tell me about the latest FedRed decision. It's classified it into Market News.
How does compound interest work?
It is general finance, which is also correct.
Give me NVIDIA's revenue figures. It is also Market News, correct?
What happened to Silicon Valley Bank? Market News? Again, correct?
What is dollar cost averaging? It is general finance. Can you explain what a hedge fund is? It is?
general finance. So we saw that
It… it was able to answer
all of the, like, most of the questions correctly, only one question was wrong here.
Right? It was only one question.
was wrong here.
Apart from it, all the questions were right.
But we want all the questions to be right, right? So how can we optimize our routing here?
Okay. Internally, what happens?
For each of the routes, it will have a 0.5
threshold. So, course and similarity should be 0.5.
If the cosine similarity of the query and this is 0.5, then it will…
consider it as, uh…
consider it as the same embedding that
Uh, as the same route as the embedding was…
present in the semantic router.
But we can optimize that threshold.
Yeah, threshold list, how much cosine similarity should we?
SS width.
Okay? For each of the individual routes.
So, semantic router provides us with this threshold optimization technique.
Where you can get all the thresholds, and you can see it is 0.5 for all of the different routes that we have.
Okay?
What I can do here is provide it with, uh, training data.
So, here I've created a training data for stock analysis, for market news, for general finance, all of those things.
0.5 is the default that the programmer of semantic router created.
Okay? Now, we are going to tweak this threshold so that our accuracies
Uh, our accuracy is improved here.
So you can see, what is PE ratio for Amazon? It is stock analysis. So, we are…
creating our dataset.
After creating our dataset, we are also providing none examples.
Okay, we are example… we are providing examples for non-questions as well, like, what is the weather in Mumbai tomorrow?
write me a poem, all of those things.
We have provided it as none here.
After that, we are going to create…
Uh, X train and Y train.
any machine learning engineer, this should be…
you should be able to understand this, but if you don't,
So, what we are doing here is, we are creating two separate
Uh, lists. 1.
Which contains the question,
The other that contains the route.
Okay? After that, you can see…
that we have total 35 examples, 10 from each route, and 5 for
out-of-scope questions, okay?
After we have prepared our dataset,
We are going to…
Use this evaluate function,
And we are just…
Checking the accuracy, okay, before optimization.
And you can see…
before, like, we have optimized our threshold.
the accuracy is 68.57.
Yeah? Overall accuracy from all the examples that we shared here is 68.
57, and…
These are the default thresholds, which are… which is 0.5.
So we are going to train it now. So…
Here, you can see…
We are going to use this semantic router.
dot fit method, and pass in our x train invitering, which means we pass in our
route, and…
We pass in the, uh…
the question, and the route for that question.
Okay? You're passing the route, the question, and the route for that question.
After it has been optimized, you can see the thresholds,
have changed, okay?
From 0.5 now, stock analysis threshold is…
0.74. Market news threshold is 0.61.
And general finance threshold is 0.6540.
After we have done this, you can see the accuracy has improved by…
two points here, which is not much.
But this tells you that
Uh, the core idea here was not to improve the accuracy to 90% or something, but to tell you how to improve it, actually.
Okay? To show you how to improve it. If you update the examples, if you… if you create, you know, better examples and all of those things,
This can, uh, improved.
much better as well.
Okay? So we did that, now we are going to test it with a couple of
New examples that we did not provide in our training data.
And after, like, testing, you can see…
that we have some 3 wrong answers.
And our text accuracy is 72%.
Okay? And most of the answers that it has…
Prompted to are correct.
Okay? I can see a lot of questions. I'm going to answer them.
Those of you, like, who do not have any questions, whose doubt is clear, just go through. I request all of you…
to go through the whole code. Once again, I will provide a recap after answering the questions that we have here, okay?
So let me answer the questions here, and then we will do a quick recap.
So, do we have to pass so many questions every time? Is there a generic way to give the data? We do not have to pass so many questions every time.
Uh, you only need to pass the question that the user has asked.
Okay.
to this intent classifier. You only need to pass the question that the user has asked.
If you do that, uh…
And this is a one-time thing.
While building this application, while building this routing layer,
Only at that time, you need to…
add all of these examples, do the threshold optimization and everything.
After you have created your router, you can use that router.
And during inference, you just pass a question, it will…
Select the route.
We did not split the dataset because we created a different test dataset altogether. Got them.
Okay?
What is X train, Y train? Could you explain? So, uh, X-Train Y-train is a terminology that
this particular library has picked up from machine learning.
So, in machine learning, what happens is…
You have some input.
And you have some expected output.
Okay? You call the expected… you call the input provided X, and you call the expected output.
as Y, you give this data of
of input and expected output for the particular input.
to an ML model, the ML model learns the pattern.
in that data, and… and get strained.
to predict on any new input.
Okay? So that's the same terminology here. So here,
We know that our input was the question.
And our output was this route.
Okay? That is why we have used X train for question, Y train for route,
And we have used it to…
optimize our…
semantic router threshold.
Which is similar to training an ML model.
Okay.
How is it calculating the accuracy? So, it is just checking. Out of all the 35 questions, how many were answered correctly, how many were answered?
Uh, wrong. So it is just calculating the percentage.
Where model store training, for next instance use.
For next instance use, if…
Uh, in the semantic router itself, if you provide a vector DB or some kind of persistent storage,
I will show you in the documentation how to do that.
If you provide those things, then it will store it in the DB that you provide.
Okay? And it can be used directly from there.
So, recap needed for accuracy. You… I hope you all understand what accuracy is now.
I just…
explained accuracy, yeah? Everybody, make sense what accuracy is?
It is just the percentage of correct answers.
Okay.
Out of all the training data that you give, what is the
Percentage of correct answers.
Utterances is also like training data, yes. Utterances are like the training data. Utterances are the actual
uh… like, the actual embeddings that will be stored. So, embeddings will be created for utterances, and they will be stored.
in the semantic router.
Do we always have finite route decided by humans?
You should always have final route decided by humans. Otherwise,
what is even the purpose of routing?
Right? Uh, we do routing…
to provide a definite set of…
Um, I could say a definite set of…
parts for the LLM to take.
If you have infinite number of routes,
then it… it, you know, is equivalent to having no route at all.
Can we use knowledge distillation to train a small model?
to do classification, will it be an overkill?
Uh, you do not need knowledge distillation to train a small model for classification.
You can fine-tune it.
to do classification again.
We will discuss about this when we talk about fine-tuning.
folks, don't worry. Uh…
Our way of teaching is teaching simple things first, and then connecting them together in the end.
Okay? So…
You saw embeddings, you saw vector stores.
Now, just see how the…
how embedding is used, uh, was being used.
to build rack pipelines.
Now, the same embedding concept is being used for routing as well.
Okay? So, focus on… if you had not focused on embedding, you won't understand routing.
just focus on the topic that is being discussed right now.
you'll be able to figure out
everything, uh, later.
Yes, Gautam.
What percentage of data is required to build
a training dataset.
It depends upon your use case and…
Yeah.
how complex is the problem that you're solving? How many routes do you have?
Right now, for us,
For us, folks, what do you think?
the kind of classification we are doing in routes.
Is it simple, or is it a bit complicated?
Simple? Do you guys really think it is simple? Because, see,
We have stock analysis, we have market news, and we have general finance.
If I give all of these
utterances to any human, and ask them,
to classify them correctly.
Do you think a human will be able to 100%?
like, classify them with 100% accuracy?
No, right? Because…
It is… yeah, all the three routes.
have… kind of have an overlap.
Among each other, right? All these three routes
have very… have an overlap.
with each other. They are very closely related.
Right? So this is not an easy data set. We are…
Working with the complicated data set, because…
They are very closely related.
So, if you are… if you are using semantic embedding, something like that,
Then semantic embedding for
One finance question. Compared to semantic abandoning of other finance questions will be very close to each other, right?
the borders will be very blurred.
for each of these different
utterances.
Yeah? That is why, you see, there was no…
uh, like, no wrong classification in general finance, but
When it comes to market news, and when it comes to stock analysis, it was…
Uh, there is a lot of overlap.
Yep.
How to achieve 100% accuracy?
Nobody knows the correct answer to this.
But, yeah, you can achieve…
very decent accuracy.
Uh, if…
like I'll tell you, in production scenario, how I will use something like this.
So, I will create a huge data.
I will take an embedding model, I will fine-tune the embedding model on the data that I have generated.
Okay? After that, I will create new routing examples, new utterance examples.
And provide those utterance examples to my routes.
And then use the fine-tuned model that I used.
that I created with this semantic router.
And classify my, like, do my routing.
That will give me, like, 80-90% accurate result.
Okay.
A lot of routing is an individual component.
Right? Think of all of these things as Lego blocks, uh, like,
Lego blocks, okay?
You… you know about agent, you know about routing. Yesterday, you built two different rack pipelines.
Now, how can you combine all of these together to build an application?
I want to leave this up to you. See?
If I give everything on the platter,
You won't become an AI engineer.
Okay? Why won't you become an AI engineer? Because?
you won't have, like, you would not have developed the critical thinking.
of designing these kind of architectures. I'm here to help you 100%, we are here to, like,
support you on Discord as well. But there are some things…
that we want you to…
do on your own, experiment on your own. We are teaching you all the building blocks that are needed to become great AI engineer.
You play with that LEGO set, right? You remember, right?
How many of you have kids?
Give me a raise of hand if you have kids.
Yeah. So…
When your kid is really small,
to, uh…
to actually, like, you know,
help them develop the critical thinking. You give them the LEGO bricks, right?
you… you give them LEGO bricks, you…
uh, build very tiny structures, and you let them play with it.
You just observe how they are playing with it.
Uh, sometimes they build a bridge, sometimes they build…
a train platform, a house, whatever.
Okay? Similarly, I'm providing you these LEGO bricks.
You built, uh,
like, whatever you want to, and ask for our help.
When you are stuck. Okay, we'll help you out.
But experimentation, practice,
Combining these concepts together to build some application is a must.
You should absolutely, absolutely do that.
And do this practice. We mentioned it in the first session itself. Without practice,
Uh, hold two months are useless.
Trust me, I'm saying this. Without practice,
Cold 2 months are useless. You must have… you may have learned some jargons. You can execute this code in Notebook.
But you won't be able to build good applications, okay? That's why we are providing you assignments,
that are, uh…
you know, that are very similar to something that you will build in the industry. And you will get an assignment,
Uh, after today as well, okay? So tomorrow, keep an eye on Discord, we will…
provide you an assignment on RAG.
Where you would have to use the concept of
Uh, embeddings of…
rack pipeline that you learned, and also routing.
Okay? You have to use concepts of all of that.
And build that RAP pipeline.
Can we provide files as data in route config? Yeah. So, semantic… yeah, you can provide it in form of JSON.
So, let me, uh, take you to…
Let me share the documentation of Semantic Router, okay?
So…
semantic router, you can see it has…
People 9 stars.
And here, in the documentation, when you see,
then you can create indexes.
in Postgres, Pinecone,
You can use Quadrant as well.
Okay? So they provide all of these.
And uh… in getting started examples, you can see, like,
You can… you can use JSON as well.
to store. So…
Just check it.
It should be there somewhere.
Save load from file.
So, you can provide it a JSON of all the routes.
You can create a JSON of all the routes.
And just import that JSON.
Okay? Layer.jsn.
You can import that JSON directly.
So you can do all of those things.
I'm providing this documentation with you, you can explore it in depth.
And experiment with it.
Yeah?
Is there a possibility of tie of route selection?
Yeah, usually, like, uh, I think internal implementation is such that…
In case of a tie, they give it to, like,
Uh, they choose one random…
How would you handle a request that requires multiple agents?
We will talk about it, Satya, when we built multi-agent systems.
Isn't tool calling also kind of semantic routing?
Uh, LLM decides which tool to call.
But semantic routing is for deciding
the agent itself. Let's say you have multiple agents, you're building multiple agents in your pipeline,
Just like the example yesterday, okay? We…
we had two different track pipelines. One was…
for answering FAQs, one was for fetching live ticket data.
from SQL.
So, you can create two routes.
Or you can create multiple routes, like, 3 routes.
And from all of those routes,
You can add utterances, one, like, one set of utterance,
For the questions that you may get.
from the document or the Q&A.
For other, you can create…
questions regarding their ticket.
Okay? From the DB.
And, uh, another route you can create for any off-topic questions.
After doing that,
You will have…
access to this route that got generated, right?
You will have access to this particular route here.
So, let's say the route is…
Uh, here, let's say the route is stock analysis.
Okay? There, that out could be Q&A.
There could be two routes, Q&A, or…
SQL. If the route is Q&A, you just
you just check. So here you see, right?
We have this, uh, semantic router, we are passing in the query, we are getting in this result.
So you can check. If result,
dot name equals equals…
SQL, call the SQL agent.
If result.name equals equals FAQ,
Call the FAQ agent, okay?
or the FAQ rack pipeline, any of those.
So, you need to write a simple if-else block.
To make this call.
Okay?
Is it allowed to fine-tune embedding model? Uh, yes, it is allowed to fine-tune embedding model, and fine-tuning is something that you do not need to do every time.
Uh, you can do it once.
Any other way to…
Uh, train router, apart from exchange wire chain tuppers.
Uh, no, that is the way that they have suggested.
Is there ability to ta- okay?
Apart from assignment, can you share problem statements on every week session so that we can do it in free time?
Okay, sure. Uh…
Maybe in Discord you can ask.
for any problem statement, but assignments are a good way, right? Assignments…
We have designed assignments in such a way that…
You can… you get to experience real problems and solve them.
The difference between using embedding here versus RAG is that in RAG, we save them in Vector Store, but here, we did not.
Uh, no, Suprit.
Here, as well, we can save it in Vector Store.
But the purpose of using that embedding is different.
In drag, we are using those embeddings.
Fourth generation.
to generate some response from the LLM.
Here, we are using the embedding.
To, uh, do intent classification.
Okay.
Nowadays, coding agents develop code end-to-end.
End-to-end, it becomes difficult where to stop them.
like, how to go about working on developing
any application, how much?
Do ourselves how much we leverage gold.
Anurag, it means that you are not splitting the task
well with agent. I'll tell you how I use Coding agent.
I mostly write the skeleton of my project on my own.
Okay. And…
Uh, skeleton of my project means, let's say I define what my project would look like.
A folder structure. All the modules that it
Uh, it is supposed to have.
And some kind of core functions, some core functions that I need to implement, that I implement on my own.
And, uh, I just defined a function and add the pass keyword.
For the functions that I want the LLM to implement, okay?
I had a comment that implement this function, something like that.
And uh… once, like, the skeleton is ready,
I use a coding agent to generate a PRT. After
Uh, it generates a PRD based on, like, by going through my skeleton and the…
prompts that I've provided.
I verify the PRD.
like, verify the PRD really in-depth. After verifying the PRD,
I ask it to generate, uh…
tasks, if the PRD is correct.
After, like, end the task it generates is always in phases, okay?
So, then I do the implementation phase by phase. So, after it has implemented phase one,
I would review what code it has written.
If there is any change that is supposed to be made,
I review that code, add those changes in the review comments.
And uh… then I move on to the phase 2, phase 3.
make this… so… so…
If you just ask it, give a task in one go, it will…
keep on generating XOS tokens, do all of those things, but if you use…
this kind of a methodology, I think it will be a lot better.
So, embedding models are trained using ML.
Does that mean I need to learn? No, no.
Uh, no, I am, uh…
When we talk about fine-tuning, you will understand these things, okay?
Uh, Gaurav?
It is… it is not very difficult.
to transfer this. So, I'll tell you one thing.
Just take all the code that we have written here,
Okay? Take all the code that we have written here.
or give this notebook to Claude.
And ask Claude that
convert this notebook experiment.
into a modular Python project.
Just… just use this.
convert this…
notebook to modular Python project.
It will create…
a modular Python project for you, you will see the code that we have written here is not going to change.
Only thing that will change is…
It will create a requirement.txt file.
And instead of…
These commands that we have here, like pip install,
Langchain and everything. It will just…
add all of these in requirement.txt file.
Or, if it is using poetry, or UV, anything else, it will create the pyproject.tunnel.
Then, instead of this, it will use .env.
just… here, it will import .env.
load.env.
create a .env file.
And add it. So…
Let's understand. The core thing here is…
Are you able to understand the core concepts that we are sharing, like, about agents, about…
brag about…
All the semantic router and everything?
If you're able to understand that,
And you have back-end experience already?
You can use the backend experience to just transfer this code.
transfer this code to…
a backend project. We will do… we will do that.
Okay, we will do that. But if you are…
Really in a hurry to do something like that, to experiment and do something like that.
Just try it out on your own. Fail.
Ask question in Discord.
We will help you. We will unblock you there.
Yeah? Gaurav, have you tried?
converting, like, transferring this into…
Python project?
Yeah?
And what happened?
When you tried that?
So you're already doing it, right? Which is a good thing. So…
Yeah, just… just send the error on Discord.
don't send it personally to me, send it in the channels, because
Even if I'm not available, somebody else will be able to help you out there.
Okay? So, folks,
There is… there is a skill that we talked about, right, in the first session itself, which is high agency.
Uh, do you know why?
trivial software programs did not…
Uh, like, did not have this much of an hype, and why…
Agents have this much of a hype.
Do you know why?
It is because of agency. Agents have high agency. They can do a lot of tasks on their own.
You do not have to click a bunch of buttons.
Okay? They reduce your work.
similarly, if you as an AI engineer
Uh, if there is only one skill that you need to learn really well, it is
going to be high agency.
Yeah. Humans are inherently lazy, but see, that's the difference, right? If you… if you have chosen this field, which is difficult,
You want to pursue a difficult field.
then you would have to do difficult things.
You cannot…
choose a difficult field, and…
not have agency to do those things, right?
So, agency… high agency is one of the core qualities that
AI engineers.
should have, because these things are changing so fast.
In previous patch, I was talking about Langstream community. In this batch, Langstream Community is deprecated.
But the core concepts.
they always stay.
What is needed here is
the agency to experiment by removing landscape.
Community dependencies with whatever new things that they have suggested.
Core things going to remain same. You're still going to…
download a model from Hugging Face. If Hugging Face gets replaced by, let's say, something like Angry Face, you just need to download the model from Angry Face. You need to figure out how to do that.
In the end, core principle is going to remain same. You want an embedding
to do efficient search,
semantic search. After doing efficient semantic search, you need to pass the LLM, provide the LLM with context.
And get response, okay? Yeah, okay, this could be the logo for Angry Face.
Yeah.
Uh, Gautam, the core focus, again, should be on the core
core concepts, yeah? What are the core concepts here?
You see, embedding is a core concept.
Semantic embedding is a core concept.
You see how semantic embedding propagated?
throughout this whole lecture. It was… it was part of the second lecture.
But tell me one lecture where we have not used semantic embedding.
Yeah? So, that is something that… that is essential to know about.
Then, there is also RAG. Yeah, what is RAG? RAG is a technique to generate answers.
from models. Yeah, by providing them context from some kind of a data source.
So, all the concepts, all the theoretical concepts that we are talking here, and the techniques that we are discussing in the code, not the code itself, but the techniques that we are discussing in this code.
Yeah? Those things are, like, really important.
No, you don't need calculus if you are working on the application side.
So folks, try to understand. There are…
multiple different areas of AI where you can work.
You have the research,
Uh, side, where…
you are focusing on building new models, okay?
There, you need… really need to be good at maths, you really need to know calculus, you need to…
no information theory you need to know linear algebra.
statistics, all of those things.
And build models. So, I was, uh, like, I did deep learning, uh, I was a deep learning engineer earlier,
And there, I was required to know some amount of calculus.
a lot of statistics and linear algebra.
But now, because of…
GenAI, like,
We have the application layer of AI.
Where you need to use a pre-existing model,
integrate it in your application and build application with it.
If you do that, you do not need a lot of maths knowledge. Whatever maths is required, we will cover here.
You do not need to know a lot of maths, but
What you need to know well
is engineering?
the AI concepts that we are teaching
Here, trust me, when we were designing this curriculum, we…
have thought a lot of things through. We have done a lot of analysis of
different job portals, what, what…
What skills are needed, our own experience of building AI products at ATLIC, at
code basics, everything.
And, uh, our prior experiences in our… in the different companies that we worked at.
And trust me, the core skills that we are teaching,
You… if you know that,
Uh, if you practice it well,
That's… that's more than enough.
to become, you know, a good AI engineer.
I'll tell you, like, in the previous cohort,
a person wrote a research paper.
based on whatever he learned here.
Yeah, he conducted a research on his own, and he wrote a research paper.
So, let's…
See some other questions. Can we use AI agent to generate images, video? Which model to use? We can use AI agent to generate
Uh… you can use…
Gemini…
I think you can use Google Omni model.
Okay? Mano Vanana is there.
GPT image is there.
Uh, there is also…
flux models, which are open source, you can use them.
In Agentic AI, usage of tools that we discussed today, can we interpret the response?
from LLM. Paranganatam, can you please elaborate your question a little bit more?
How do you want to interpret the response? Uh…
I need more context to answer this.
To get into research, what's the path?
I'm already a software developer with 8 years of experience.
To get into research,
you need to know maths really well.
You need to read a lot of research papers.
Uh, starting from, I think,
If you read research papers from 2016, 20… no, I think 20…
12. If you start from AlexNet,
After reading about AlexNet, if you start
with, uh…
Attention paper, not the attention is all you need. There was a paper before that.
Where RNN-based attention algorithm was used.
then attention is all you need.
After retention is all you need, all the OpenAI, DeepSeek,
Lama, uh, if you read all of those papers, and you start implementing models,
On your own. Like, use PyTorch, learn PyTorch.
We have a PyTorse tutorial in the recorded bootcamp, in deep learning module.
Learn PyTorch. Learn how transformer models work.
Uh, the internals of everything, like positional encoding, then there is a query key-value pairs.
gave me cash, all of those things.
Learn how transformative models work. Implement.
your own transformer model.
spend some money.
in renting a GPU,
training that transform model, and then…
see how you can optimize it, create any new component,
for… in the transformer model to optimize it.
Publish your own research paper.
Once you publish a couple of your own research papers, you can break into, like,
research.
Also, we are understanding the concepts, however, it seems very difficult to write code.
For even simple pipeline, Hema, this is because…
You are not practicing enough.
So, how many of you, like, when you learned
programming for the very first time.
Were you able to code in…
The next week of learning,
Programming? Were you able to code programs, like, in the next week of learning programming?
First, you would learn the concepts, then you would learn how to create a flowchart.
Then you would learn how to convert that flowchart into a running code, working code, right?
Similar things you need to do here as well.
I think the mistake that you're making is you learned all these concepts in
You want to directly build the pipeline.
First, use pen and paper.
draw the components, what all components you need, how…
We are going to implement it.
Then move on to writing code.
Okay.
They're not going to cover anything else in the session.
Uh, let's… let's have Slido. I think. Any other questions that you have, you can…
Ask it in Discord, I'll answer it.
So, Prasanna has asked, I have no prior experience in coding.
What I'm trying to learn, do you have any suggestion or guidance for people like me?
Persona, right now, like…
If you know good English, if you know all these concepts well, you can use an AI agent to code, okay? So I would say you start
Using the AI agent… agents to…
write code for you, but…
read everything that they are generating, and try to understand the code.
You can go through the Python module,
to learn Python, okay?
And after, like, going through the Python module to learn Python, you will understand a lot of the concepts that are used.
in writing that code, and it will be useful for you.
Can we create cache memory kind of thing, so we don't use LLM? I said Satyam, any kind of
Question that you have specific to your…
project, you can ask it in…
So, we can create cache,
But we will discuss caching and all of those things later on, okay? There's something called semantic caching, we will discuss it in optimization lecture.
As an example you gave,
Role-based, route-based on tools, stock analysis market, yeah.
If there are 100 different tools, then do we have to prepare?
Uh, no, see.
Uh, this example…
take it as an example only.
If you have 100 different tools, you can cluster those tools into different groups, okay?
There will be a specific kind of task, a specific kind of agent that will require to do a specific kind of
Uh, like, that will require, let's say, 5 or 6 different tools, yeah? So you can clust… you can take…
cluster of those tools, and then…
use the, um…
create route for only that cluster. So you'll… you will create route for the number of different pipelines you have, or the number of different agents that you have.
to choose from. Not each and individual tools that you have.
Krishna, can we start the Slido? So, folks, let's start with the Slido.
Uh, if you have a lot more questions, you can ask the questions in Discord and tag me.
I will try to answer your questions there, okay?
I'm gonna share my screen
Is it prison
Yes.
Alright, folks. You can either scan this QR code, or go to slido.com and type this code
Let's see…
We have someone called intent.
I think you have joined as well.
Somebody is impersonating me, I have not joined.
Okay. I'll keep my hands like this throughout the quiz.
Alright, should we wait for that? 10 more seconds? I think I'm still joining.
Okay, we have Tony Stark as well. So, see, I am competing with Tony Stark, okay? Whoever is using my name,
Please do not come last.
It's Dhaval Patel also, but I think this is not an impersonation
That's his real name. There is… we have two Dhalpatins.
Dawal, if you can turn on your camera so that we can verify you are a real person.
Thank you
Should we wait for, like, 10 more seconds?
Yeah, let's wait for 10 more seconds, and…
We have, we shall overcome.
Oh, there's Andrew NG.
Oh, wow. See, I have a lot of competition here.
Yeah
But I'm glad there is no Andrei Karpathy.
Just wait for a while.
It would have been really difficult if there were any Andre Kalbots.
Alright, should we start?
Yes, let's start.
Okay, let's go to first question.
What enables an AI agent to perform tasks on your behalf
I think it's definitely the coffee one, but that's just my opinion.
So, Krishna answers correctly when it is on chat, but she will mislead you when it is.
you know, live in Zoom.
People thanks for it.
Yeah, someone called, you know, someone fell into my trap. Yeah, let's see.
Okay, 99%.
You can move the Andrew NG, Tony Stark, Karthik Prabhu, and Abhira.
Sid, what are you doing, ma'am?
Okay, let's go to the next
Okay. As agency increases, predictability tends to dash
See, I think we focused quite a lot of time on this.
Mixed
And so it's the correct answer. Okay, decrease because the system has more freedom to make decisions
People are getting a lot of confused, I think.
Uh, I'll answer this in a very simple way. So…
Like, agency and predictability are inversely proportional to each other.
Okay? Which means that if agency increases,
Predictability will decrease.
If predictability increases, which means that you have to compromise with agency.
Okay? Both of them cannot increase at the same time.
They… they are inversely proportional to each other.
All right, we have Andrew Engie on top. Then move CR Renganathan, Karthik Robhu, and Anupam Saraswattha
Let's go
What is the correct sequence in a react route?
I think this is
Pretty straightforward
But there are a lot of confusing options.
Okay, let's see
It's thought, action, and observation. I think 30% people got a little confused
Okay? I think same reader board. Andrew and G, Murthy are Anupam Saraswat, Karthik Prabhu, and Sushma. No, minor changes.
What is the system prompt best used for?
Making the LLM to stay in topic
I think 5% people are just messing with me
Let's see the correct answer.
Setting the agent's roles and boundaries
Okay. Oh, I think Andrew and Jay left the leaderboard. Anupam Saraswat, Muttihar, Zai Sri Ram, Anil, and Kardim Raman.
Okay, what is the role of a check pointer and line graphs?
It saves and restores
It saves and restores agent state format to turn memory
I think 12% people got confused.
Okay. Anupang Saraswat Murthi are Anil Akilesh, and Tony Stark.
Okay. Which framework is best for handling multi-step reasoning with branching logic?
I think your brain seems correct.
It definitely does that.
Let's see… Landgrav, that's correct, 91%.
Alright, we have Anupam Saraswat, Murthy R, Tony Star, Saishri Ram, and Vignesh Raja Kunpath
Okay.
What is the process of directing a user request to the appropriate agent tool or workflow pod
Okay, 95% routing
Yeah, so routing is the correct answer.
Oh, we have an homatyar, Tony Stark, Sai Sri Ram, and Ame Beati
Okay, this is the last question, so back up, guys.
Semantic router uses Dash to make routing decisions.
Vector embeddings is the correct answer
Right. Oh, congratulations on Bonsai Swat Murthyar, Tony Stark, Saishiram, and Karthik Prabhu
Great work.
I would like to give the stage.
to Android NG?
And sit.
whoever was set code basics, and uh…
Android. Okay, Adil wasid.
Okay.
Alright, who was Andrew Engie?
Oh, Golden Wars and Rainy, okay.
Nice. Alright, folks.
Uh, that's it from our end today.
Hope you had a good time, hope you learned a lot.
Congratulations on building your first agent.
I would like you to experiment more.
And come up with, like, new examples.
Keep an eye on Discord for the assignment.
Okay? Uh…
Yeah, anything that you want to say, uh, please go ahead.
Yesterday, I mentioned that I would showcase
project that you have built, assignment that you have built. So, if anybody wants to share any project,
We can spend, like, 10 more minutes.
to showcase any assignment.
Anybody wants to showcase their project?
mentioned in the chat.
No, Langchain is…
Right. I think nobody wants to share their project.
Okay, folks, see you next week. Have a good time.
Yeah, bye.